<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inspired Labs</title>
    <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Inspired Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Phillips</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>I design and deliver projects for organisations such as National Geographic, Siemens, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and ambitious startups.
My work applies thorough, user-friendly design that moves projects forward. These can be greenfield projects like attention engineering for Aris Technologies. Or a communication strategy for Vaultarch, an award‑winning deep‑tech company.
Currently, my focus is content design for the mobile web. This includes graphic design, rapid prototyping and writing templates. I&amp;rsquo;m enthusiastic about combining performant code, aesthetics and accessibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Coach</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/alessandroronca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/alessandroronca/</guid>
      <description>Multilingual booking Written in HUGO and deployed to NetlifyCMS for speed and simplicity this site helps people understand the health benefits of cold exposure.
Securing bookings as an Ice Coach and educator Alessandro Ronca vividly explains the benefits of The Wim Hof Method in Italian and English.
Challenge Accepted! Forseen technical challenges included:
 NetlifyCMS does not officially support multilingual sites. high-quality templates for Schema.org poorly documented.  Both solutions were possible by writing complex templates with nested data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RVO.LT</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/rvolt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/rvolt/</guid>
      <description>Beyond Sustainability The platform shares 20 years of learning about domestic and community sustainability.
The aim is to connect other design sucesses with people across disciplines.
Areas of focus Designed with Generalists in mind, the project brings attention to key areas of change: Health, Education, Food, Transport and Shelter.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t focused on countries finding ways to justify the costs of managing the Climate Crisis – but how design should raise life quality for billions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marzò</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/marzoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/marzoli/</guid>
      <description>Communicating family values A warm, welcoming website clear for local people looking for fresh, organic produce. Yet appealing to food connoisseurs, even overseas.
Powerful tools for nimble pages This mobile first eCommerce site runs via NetlifyCMS, a web interface for writers. A static site generator called HUGO produces flat files without a database. This combination scores highly with Google PageSpeedInsights.
Manageable styling Tachyons adapts to design needs. By patching existing classes fixes limitations in the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locality</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/localitysite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/localitysite/</guid>
      <description>Co-habitation Property Services This webapp helps people in the luxury rental market organise and filter rooms to taste.
JSON sanitisation in NetlifyCMS The filter takes JSON data and renders it client-side keeping the information up-to-date without having any other build process.
Terse code output from HUGO templates, catches data entry errors. This investment makes maintaining nuances in the properties as simple as possible.
Visit Locality.site </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Smith Photography</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/sebastian-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/sebastian-smith/</guid>
      <description>An eye for detail Busy with photography clients such as Naomi Campbell, Kim Kardashian and Martina Navratilova, Sebastian Smith occasionally needs to retouch shoots.
…and with clients like these Seb requires a keen eye for detail.
Working together on these images involves repairing blemishes, performing complex repairs and preparing hairstyles for large-format advertising.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaultarch</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/vaultarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/vaultarch/</guid>
      <description>Award winning Ltech startup Cambridge University&amp;rsquo;s Andrew Buchanan, set out to make counterfeit, theft and fraud a thing of the past: Vaultarch is a multi award winning Ltech (Legal tech) startup protecting valuable collectables.
 Scott displayed energy &amp;amp; resourcefulness… He has good networking skills &amp;amp; an eye for the commercial factor – Andrew Buchanan, Vaultarch  Visit  Vaultarch.com Startup Weekend Startup Next Facebook Twitter Cyberport2, Hong Kong   Project in detail Why is Vaultarch important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PeR, Il Parco dell Energia Rinnovabile</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/per/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/per/</guid>
      <description>The largest independent, sustainability research center in Italy Deep in an area of outstanding natural beauty With limited resources, such as no water, lead by engineer and entrepreneur Alessandro Ranco a small team has built on an ancient site. Adding power, irrigation, and a teaching block on top of where they live PeR has become the largest facility of it&amp;rsquo;s kind in Italy.
 …the tools exist to design better communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM platform</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/3si/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/3si/</guid>
      <description>3Si: 20 years of CRM development Who are 3Si, and what they do? Derived from their surname Chris Sinclair, Pete Sinclair, and their Father – a silent partner, 3Si sell their CRM application to handle volumes of membership and subscription data. Their flagship product is called OM.Net.
Client work The OM.Net platform is for Nonprofit Organisations such as Mensa, The National Farmer&amp;rsquo;s Union and Trading Standards. I was also concerned with the web platform for The Pathological Society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carfax Gardens at Carfax Tower</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/fernandos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/fernandos/</guid>
      <description>Carfax Cafe, Oxford In 2012 entrepreneur, Fernando Kindermann opened Smiley Cafe. Friendly hospitality and Brazilian and Italian dishes are served from the shadowy site – although, that formula wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough. The venue struggled to attract passing trade and consistent regulars. To help the Carfax Tower stand-out, we used design to attract people and boost sales…
 The Project in detail Meet here for Breakfast, Lunch &amp;amp; Tea The business needed a rebrand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M&#43;H Awards Winner</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/museums-heritage-awards-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/museums-heritage-awards-winner/</guid>
      <description>A huge achievement, against all odds The Children’s Centre for Civilisation &amp;amp; Creativity, Heliopolis, Egypt endured the usual construction challenges. In 2011, the timing of the Arab-spring and Egyptian revolution further complicated things for Mallinson&amp;rsquo;s Architects &amp;amp; Engineers&amp;rsquo; team.
Mallinson&amp;rsquo;s winning the Museum + Heritage award in 2012 because of well organised design. Together, collaborators solved problems outside Egypt so the holistic design became a reality.
Beyond content creation Project background Appointed to create mixed digital media, including games, touch interfaces and animating a double-sided, 30 metre LED wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowers &amp; Wilkins</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/bowers-and-wilkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/bowers-and-wilkins/</guid>
      <description>Conference opener Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins make the worlds most advanced hi-fi products. Partnering with Apple, Jaguar and Lucasfilm, I was brought onboard by Thomas Manss, to celebrate their “true sound” in-car audio products for the Vintage at Goodwood conference.
Legacy Turning 2D illustrations into versatile storytelling elements, we created a memorable musical short overcoming many hurdles. This introduced delegates to the annual conference – to rapturous applause.
 Project in detail Thomas Manss creates something remarkable The outline of the brief was to tell the evolutionary story of Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, under strict oversight of the talented art-director: Thomas Manss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InstantWebapp</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/instantwebapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/instantwebapp/</guid>
      <description>Philosophy Reduce investment risk Intended for entrepreneurs to control their costs, and guarantee content delivery to their customer&amp;rsquo;s devices.
Responsible design Meeting business goals, controlling costs and avoiding gotchas does not mean generic, undesirable websites. Delighting the user is easier when the same constraints apply across organisations. Design templates lay the groundwork.
Advancing marketing campaigns, content and aesthetics on top of a sound foundation is better than spending on reinvention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aris Technologies</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/aris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/aris/</guid>
      <description>Secure, sophisticated software Aris Technologies develop their own online gaming platform for a niche market. The company is organised to follow the sun, writing code during GMT, tested in China and constantly deployed to the US market.
Project Legacy Templates designed remain in use for this “development A-Team”, providing a decent return on investment tp meets Aris&amp;rsquo; business demands.
 The project in detail Template driven user interface design As the lead user interface designer, realised the templates for a broad range of games – from roulette, to video slots within Flash and within a 3D environment using OpenGL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Animations</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2005 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/advanced/</guid>
      <description>An impressive heritage About Advanced Advanced Animations is a traditional technical drawing office offering services Rolls Royce and innovators such as:Siemens, Cummins and other household names.
Although, their heritage hasn&amp;rsquo;t made them immune to technological progress.
Legacy Brought on board specifically to modernise business practices, we formed the foundation of a new business model – providing them a robust ROI years into the future.
 About the project Updating workflow and business model Simply put areas of the business were reduced to templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Generalist CV</title>
      <link>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungry-wozniak-e915f8.netlify.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your consideration, I hope this information finds you well.
My content development work focuses on performant code. Rarely relying on complex dependencies or configurations, I aim to work at the correct abstraction layer, keeping things accessible.
Responsive Web Design  I have a strong preference for static site generation with HUGO. Deploy to GitHub, served from Netlify. Using Service Workers for offline capabilities. Custom, modular layouts based on Tachyons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>